# SVAY THAVIRAK

#### **PROFILE**

My name is SVAY THAVIRAK joined UDAYA Technology since October 2019. I has experience of API Developer. In Current Job Sovichet is responsible data for mobile developer and Frontend developer (API), develop company software product with development team. I had using Java Spring Boot Framework and using MySQL for fetch data from Database for build API for any company product.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 070 933 433

EMAIL:

thaavirak@gmail.com

ADDRESS:

#16G, ST. 2A, Phum Krol Kor, Sangkat Kilo6, Khan Russey Keo, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

Per

### **HOBBIES**

Surfing internet Researching Traveling Sport

## **EDUCATION**

SETEC Institute 2017 - 2021

Graduated bachelor degree on majoring Management of Information Technology

Australia Center of Education (ACE) 2016 - 2018 Graduated General English Program with IELTS score of 5.5

The Westline School 2013 - 2016 Graduated Adult English Program

Baktouk High school 2017 Graduated diploma

## QUALIFICATION AND TRAINING COURSE

ANT Technology Training Center 2018 – 2019

- Completed HTML course
  - Completed CSS and Bootstrap course
  - Completed C# Beginner course
  - Completed JavaScript course

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Udaya Technology, (Internship as ReactJS Developer and UI & UX Design) September 2019 – November 2020

- Use Figma as a tool to design prototypes for web and mobile applications
- Learn ReactJS's fundamental and practice to build web applications
- Learn and practice new JavaScript syntax (ES6)

Udaya Technology, (Frontend Developer) November 2020 - Present

- Developed Frontend design using ReactJS for the project (Logistic, Payroll System, Electronic Medical Records System, GPS Tracking, etc...)
- Self-learning and using Node-Red to build Telegram Bot (Bot be able to send reports using API data to Telegram User)
- Self-learning and using NodeJS to build Messenger Bot (Bot be able to show food menu, receive order from user and send to seller's dashboard)
- Using NodeJs and ExpressJs to build API endpoints

- Update customers' feature requests and updates on demand
- Support and maintain existing software
- Apply technical processes to solve complex problems
- Prioritize software development projects, set timelines and assign tasks to completed on time
- Build Applications for deploy to Apache Tomcat Server

## **SKILLS**

### Hard Skills

September 2019 - November 2020

- Use Figma as a tool to design prototypes for web and mobile applications
- Learn ReactJS's fundamental and practice to build web applications
- Learn and practice new JavaScript syntax (ES6)
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, MySQL
- Database Management System
- Linux, Ubuntu (Command line basic)
- Adobe Photoshop, Figma Design (UX/UI)
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access)
- Basic IT Maintenance
- Basic Accounting and payroll

## **REFERENCES**

Mr. Vann Marady
Chief Business Development Officer at Udaya Technology
Tel: 010 951 313, Email: marady@udaya-tech.com